Bosko and Honey is a comedy, animation, music film directed by Hugh Harman.
This is an unreleased cartoon that eventually went on to have most
of its animation recycled by Bosko's Dizzy Date.
Honey is trying to teach the violin to Wilbur, the one who hates music.
Honey calls Bosko over.
Bosko and Honey sing, dance, and play music while
Wilbur continues to express its disdain.
Honey (voice) (uncredited), played by Rochelle Hudson.
Bosko / Wilbur (voice) (uncredited), played by Johnny Murray.
Bosko is an animated cartoon character created by
animators Hugh Harman and Rudolf Ising.
Bosko was the first recurring character in Leon Schlesinger's cartoon series and
was the star of 39 Looney Tunes shorts released by Warner Bros.
He was voiced by Carman Maxwell, Bernard B.
Brown, Johnny Murray, and Philip Hurlic during the 1920s and
1930s and once by Don Messick during the 1990s.
The film explores themes of music teacher, anthropomorphism, short film.
The tone is lighthearted.